Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Architectural drawings, 1870-1981; Series 6; 325 item(s)
  - Fillmore School Playground Existing Condition Report, 2000 June 13; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 3)
  - Warehouse Plan Demolition, Floor Plan Architectural, Roof Plan, 2001 August 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 4)
  - Fillmore/Corcoran School of Art, 1998 February 17; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, 1989 March 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 6)
  - Warehouse Plan Demolition, Floor Plan Architectural, Roof Plan - Double Copies, 2001 August 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 7)
  - Part Plan Basement - Electrical, Floor Plan Lighting and Power, 1987; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 8)
  - Fillmore School Playground Existing Condition Plan, 2000 June 13; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 9)
  - 6015 Chillum Place Electrical Drawings, 2001 August 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 10)
  - Fillmore School Playground Existing Conditions, Site Photos, Playground Plans, 2000 May 11; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 11)
  - Fillmore School Playground Existing Conditions, Site Photos, Master Plan, Playground Plan, Playground Details, Site Plan, 2000 May 11; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 12)
  - Reflective Ceiling Plan, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.016, Item 13)
  - Headquarters Building For United Unions, Inc., 1970 March 3; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 1)
  - Headquarters Building For United Unions, Inc. copy, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 2)
  - Renovations of Row House, 1990; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 3)
  - Headquarters Building for United Unions blueprints, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 4)
  - Basic Structure, 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, 1989 March 10; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 6)
  - Security Conduit, 2003 February 7; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 7)
  - Security Planning, 2002 October 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 8)
  - Electrical/Power plans, 2003 June 17; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 9)
  - Landscape Plan, 1980 January 24; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.017, Item 10)
  - Gehry - Communications Cabling Plan, 2001 November 16; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 1)
  - Gehry - Security Planning Legend, 2002 October 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 2)
  - Gehry - Security Planning Legend Mark Ups, 2002 October 4; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 3)
  - Gehry - Security Planning Legend, 2002 June 14; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 4)
  - Gehry - Room Finish Schedule, 2003 February 7; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 5)
  - Gehry Partners Permit Plans, 2003 February 7; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 6)
  - Gehry - Alterations to Provide Accessibility for the Handicapped, 1983 June 30; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.018, Item 7)
  - Reroofing of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2008 November 3; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 1)
  - Reinforcing and Framing Plans, 2002 December 2; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 2)
  - Gehry - Corcoran Floor Plans, 2002 July 15; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 3)
  - Basic Structure Sub-Basement, Basement, First Floor, Roof (Copies), 1984 March; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 4)
  - Food Service Plans, 2003 April 18; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 5)
  - Proposed District Fur Company, 1989 February 6; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 6)
  - Corcoran Gehry Expansion elevations, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 8)
  - Bulding Maintanence Plans, 2002 December 18; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 9)
  - Corcoran Floor Plans 100 percent Progress Print, 2000 August 1; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 10)
  - Corcoran Floor Plans, annotated, 2002 July 15; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2014.019, Item 11)
  - Details of Table & Exhibit Case for Etchings Charles A Platt Architect, 1919 October 27; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 1 (NGA 82))
  - CGA 320 HP Plant 1895, CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 2 (NGA 82))
  - Blueprint, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 3 (NGA 82))
  - Misc. Architectural Drawings, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 4 (NGA 83))
  - East Building Exterior Stone Repairs National Gallery of Art, 2010 October 21; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 1)
  - Mantle Room Drawings Kevin Johnson [2 Sheets], 1992 July 14; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 2)
  - Department of Commerce - Corcoran Gallery of Art Package Fragment, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 3)
  - Corcoran Art Gallery AC Changeover Small [6 Sheets], 1935 July; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 4)
  - Corcoran Art Gallery AC Changeover Large [6 Sheets], 1935 July; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Alternatives & Additions to School of Art c. 1960 [3 Sheets, bound], CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 6)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Auditorium Exits c. 1961 [9 Sheets partially bound], CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 7)
  - Corcoran Architectural Drawings Small [26 Sheets], Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 9)
  - Corcoran Architectural Drawings Large [5 Sheets, bound], Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 10)
  - Corcoran Architectural Drawings Large [5 Sheets, bound], Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 11)
  - Corcoran Architecural Drawings Large [5 Sheets, bound], 1984 March; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 12)
  - Corcoran Architectural Drawings Large [5 Sheets, bound], 1984 March; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 13)
  - Alterations & Additions The Corcoran School of Art, 1960 May 12; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 83), Item 14)
  - Corcoran Architectural Drawings [26 Sheets], Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 3 (NGA 104))
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Hemicycle, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 1)
  - Granite Setting Plan for Corcoran Gallery [2 Sheets], 1926 July; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 2)
  - New York Avenue Elevation Corcoran Gallery, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 3)
  - Corcoran Gallery Roof Trusses, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 4)
  - Corcoran Gallery Details of Window Sills, 1926 April 10; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery Exhibition Rooms, 1926 June 04; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 6)
  - Corcoran Gallery Window Trim, 1926 June 29; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 85), Item 7)
  - Large Bench of Walnut or Oak for the Corcoran Gallery of Art, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Parking Lot, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Auditorium Projection Booth, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Plans, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Library Reception and Board Room, Circa 1990; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Driveway NY Ave & Rear Parking Lot Temp Driveway, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - 7 Copies of Basemnet Floor Plan, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Switchboard Condiut Installation, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Lot 32 Square 171 5/1970 Plans for Hand Rails in Auditorium for Sesquicentennial Exhibitions Iron Railings Auditorium, 1950; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Parking Lot Improvements 5/4/72, 1972; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Front Foor Reconstruction, 1958-1959; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Lighting Layout, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Gallery 79=09, 1979; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Alternatives to Gallery 30, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Gallery Administration Office Layout, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Lot 32 Square 171, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Exhibit "D", Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Proposed Addition to the Corcoran Gallery of Art, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Topographical Survey 3/1970, 1970 March; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Parking Lot Improvements, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Basement Floor Plan K.K. &S 1/13/1960, 1960 January 13; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Alternatives to Gallery 30, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Capital for Second Story Columns Atrium Drawing No. 2083a, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Intersection of Cheneau on 17th St Drawing No. 2153, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - FSD of all Doors from Attic to Roof Drawing No. 2103, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Details for Door Frames Marked "EF's" "D" Drawing 504, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Full Page of Interior Column, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Parking Lot: Headquarters Building United Unions Inc., Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Headquarters Building for United Unions Inc., Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - F.S. Detail of Lever Handles for N.Y. Ave Entrance Doors, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Proposed Kitchen Layout 7/11/57, 1957 July 11; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Additions to the Corcoran Gallery of Art, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 1 (NGA 81))
  - Entrance Door & Vestibule F.K. & S, 1958 June 30; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 2 (NGA 81))
  - Art School Kiln Room, Addition 9/11/62, 1962 September 11; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 3 (NGA 81))
  - Conduit Layout Basement Floor 8/20/1971, 1971 August 20; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 4 (NGA 81))
  - First Floor Plan, 2 Plans January 13 1980 F.K. & S, 1980 January 13; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 5 (NGA 81))
  - Auditorium Fire Protection & Exit Plans 3-13-61, 1961 March 13; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 6 (NGA 81))
  - Full Plans, One with Complete Detailed Instructions of Doors, etc., Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 7 (NGA 81))
  - Proposed Future Addition by Charles A. Platt, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Reflector, 1896 September 10; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Plan of Second Story Ernest Glass 1893-1984, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Proposed 1st Floor Remodeling Feb 28, 1969 F F & V, 1969 February 28; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit A, 1969 November - 1970 May; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery Exterior Ernest Flagg, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Bequests 1966 (Revoked 1968) Halpert, Edith G. - Architectural Drawings, Floor Plans of Proposed Halpert Floor & Entrance at CGA, 1996-1968; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Heating Plan for Classroom over Auditorium Wilberding Co Inc, 1961 August 07; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Architectural Records Parmelee Bequest: Street Plan of Rental Property in Cleveland, Ohio, 1941, CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Details of Square 167, Various Lots, Prepared by Wood B.Wood, 1937; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Plat of 17th & New York, Avenue Lot, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Architectural Drawing Corcoran Gallery, United Unions Buildings, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Drawings for Building Details 1) Lever Handles 2) Entrance Gate, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Progress Chart, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Architectural Drawing Vault Light Ernest Flagg 1893-1994, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Architectural Blueprints Proposed Changes to the CGA Charles A. Platt, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate Recordds Hayes Property 1935 Parkhurst Property "Edgemoor" 1938, 1935, 1938; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Architectural Drawings Platt 8/7/27, 1927 August 07; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - 1st Floor and Basement Plans Sep 21 1925 Charles A. Platt, 1925 September 21; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Floor Plans 1984, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Corcoran School of Art Studio Plans: Printmaking Ceramics, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - 17th Street Entrance Statuary, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 8 (NGA 80))
  - Design for Renovation for Clark Exhibit Cases, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 9 (NGA 80))
  - Floor Plans Flagg, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 10 (NGA 80))
  - Various Architectural Plans, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 11 (NGA 80))
  - Corcoran Gallery Exterior, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Oversize-folder 12 (NGA 80))
  - CGA Alterations to Corcoran School 1950, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - CGA Floor Plans 1963, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - CGA Alterations to Ground floor Plans 1962, CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran Floor Plans, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - CGA Garage Door c. 1964, Circa 1964; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - CGA Floor Plans 1963, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Ezekiel, Moses, Project (never executed) for Relief Sculpture for Central Pediment of Old CGA, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - CGA Gallery Elevations c. 1992, Circa 1992; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - CGA Art School Extensions c. 1961, Circa 1961; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Art School Extension, 1960 November; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - CGA Floor Plans, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - CGA Floor Plans 1960, CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Detail of plaster columns in basement (except atrium), Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Item 3)
  - Full size-plaster detail of pilasters and panels in staircase hall, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Item 1)
  - Detail of plaster cornices in atrium and atrium gallery, 2. floor., Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Item 4)
  - Fulll size plaster detail of pilasters and panels in staircase hall, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Full size detail of niche in lecture hall-hemicycle, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Fsd of cornice in all small galleries on 2. floor, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Detail of plaster cornices in atrium and atrium gallery, 2. floor., Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 87, Folder 12, Item 4)
  - Stone ornament over main entrance door, 17 st, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Full size detail of plaster work below main entrance cornice in 3 17th st. galleries, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Detail of plaster columns in basement (except atrium), Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - Full size plaster detail of ceiling ribs in 2. story galleries, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - 1/4 scale drawing showing panels across stage in hemicycle, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 5)
  - Cornice in NY Ave studios, 1. and 2. floors Stone ornament over main entrance door, 17. st, Undated; CorRG7_0 Series 6 (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 6)
- Ephemera, 1897-1908; Series 7; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Contains one scrapbook on the new building, from its opening in 1897 through gallery events of 1908. The scrapbook includes photographs of land excavation and early stages of construction as well as newsclippings on the Gallery's opening and various exhibitions until 1908.
- Personnel records, 1984-2005; Series 11
  Conditions Governing Access
  Personnel records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation. Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
  This subseries contains alphabetical personnel files and related personnel records dating from 1984-2005.
  - Adjunct faculty contracts, 1996-2001; Series 11 (Box 53)
  - Adjunct faculty contracts and files: A-M, 1997-2000; Series 11 (Box 52)
  - Adjunct faculty contracts and files: M-Z, 1997-2000; Series 11 (Box 54)
  - Personnel: FSA Healthcare pension files, 1987 January 1 - 2009 December 31; Series 11 (Box 63)
  - Legal/litigation files, 1980 January 1-1990 December 31; Series 11 (Box 13)
  - Past employees: A-H, 1984-1987; Series 11 (Box 10)
  - Past employees: I-Z, 1984-1987; Series 11 (Box 14)
  - Past employees: A-F, 1987-1991; Series 11 (Box 28)
  - Past employees: J-Z, 1984-1987; Series 11 (Box 11)
  - Past employees: G-M, 1987-1991; Series 11 (Box 29)
  - Past employees: N-Z, 1987-1991; Series 11 (Box 30)
  - Personnel files: A-B, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 55)
  - Personnel files: C-F, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 56)
  - Personnel files: G-H, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 57)
  - Personnel files: I-L, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 58)
  - Personnel files: M-N, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 59)
  - Personnel files: O-R, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 60)
  - Personnel files: S, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 61)
  - Personnel files: T-Z, 1988-2005; Series 11 (Box 62)
  - Personnel files, 1989; Series 11 (Box 8)
  - Personnel files, 1989; Series 11 (Box 9)
  - Personnel files, undated; Series 11 (Box 12)
- Operations, Series 12
  - Plumb-Elec-Glass Work, 1983; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Status Reports & Project Budgets Building Funds, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NEA Grant, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - B&G Minutes- Extracts, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Big Plan, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - B&G Minutes, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kresge and MacArthur Proposals A/C, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Works on Paper, 1979; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Steam Lines, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kresge- CAC, 1981; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CAC Proposals, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CAC- C.O.'s, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kresge Proposals, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CAC XCOM, 1980 June 9; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - B&G Meeting, 1979 September 5; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - B&G Meeting Minutes & Notes, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NEA Proposal- CliCon, 1980; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - CAC & Kresge Proposal, 1979; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kresge Fund, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Building Fund Brochure, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Punch List - CAC, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Skylight Replacement, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Air Conditioning, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - A/C Central, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sources & Applications of Building Funds, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Contractors, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Maintenance Engineer, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Priority Lists, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Building Additions, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Aud. Maintenance, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Resumees, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Auditorium Loan, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Security Equip Doors, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Folding Gates, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Basement Bids & Contrarcts, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Art Storage Basement, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Kiln Project, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Auditorium C.O.'s Architectural, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Skinker & Garrett, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ozone, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Conversions Sub-Basement, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Conversion Pedestal Room to Art School, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Auditorium, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Auditorium C.O.'s M&E, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Auditorium No. 3, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Aud. Punch List, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Anglemeyer, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - C.O.'s Auditorium, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Anglemyer Liens, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Anglemyer Case, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Anglemyer, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Steam Trap Rebuild, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Gallery 3- Office Renovation, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - SPEC DATA for Johnson T-5800 (replaces T-9000) [AH-2], undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fan Sizing Data, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Pepco Building, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Fire Marshall School/Gallery, 1983 October; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - The Ball, 1987 April 24; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Insulation/HVAC, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Chiller Log, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Reroofing (Acutal Contractors), undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mechanical Work in Progress, 1983; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Chiller- Miscellaneous, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Chiller Service & Oil Analysis, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Centravac Chiller, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Chiller Service, 1982; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Chiller Service, 1983; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Chiller Service, 1984; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Chiller Service, 1985; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Chiller Service, 1986; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - AHU's Trane Service, undated; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Chiller Maintenance, 1987; Series 12 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - General Conditions Main Building, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Asbestos, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 1680 Wisc. Ave., circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Letters/Received, 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Letters/Sent, 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Waste Mgt- New Laws, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Mail Room Machine, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Broken Glass Floor Panels Atrium, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Special Events Work Reports, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - C&P Telephone Calling Card, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - 1680 Wisc. Ave. Building Tech, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Ceramics, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Disputed Bills, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Ventilation, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Cable & Wireless, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Historic Structures Grant Application, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Phone Answer Machines, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Gen Repair- Call 5 Flashing, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - School Self Study, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Engineer, 1989; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - 10-23-4708 Telephone, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Rich Phillips- Operations Manager, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - C&P, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - AT&T, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Temperature Restrictions, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Humidity Readings, circa 1990; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 26)